Sophie Dunfield

Dartmouth, NS dunfiena@gmail.com +1 902 698 9260

I'm a recent graduate of NSCC IT Programming course. I focus on backend programming, and designing GUI componants in several languages.

For the last 10 years, I have been a chef, and 5 of those years I also worked part-time/full-time as an offset press operator and production assistant at Gaspereau Press (printer/publisher).

Work Experience

Cook

Nelson Penner's Wild Feast - Wolfville, NS August 2020 to October 2021

I've been working as a chef is various restaurants, and catering jobs for 8 years, as well as having two years culinary school experience. I have had the opportunity to experience a vast array of styles under some expert chefs, including tasting menus ranging for 6 to 16 course. I'm passionate about cooking, and have high standards of work and cleanliness.

Production Assistant

Gaspereau Press - Kentville, NS August 2016 to 2021

Offset press operator and production assistant

Baker Bari

Charts Cafe 2018 to 2020

Education

College diploma in Computer Programming

Nova Scotia Community College - Remote September 2022 to Present

AEC / DEP or Skilled Trade Certificate in Culinary Arts

Nova Scotia Community College - Kentville, NS 2012 to 2014

Horton High School - Wolfville, NS 2008 to 2012

Languages

- English Advanced
- French Fluent

Certifications and Licenses

Safe Food Handling

2024

Delf

Present

OHS

2012 to Present

Basic WHMIS Training

2012 to Present

Emergency First Aid CPR/AED Level C

2019 to 2022